

Spanish

SKILLS

· .Net

Angular

Ionic

• SQL

· .NET Blazor

Javascript

CosmoDB

LANGUAGES

• English | Advanced

Spanish | Native

HTML

CSS

https://www.pedromg.dev

# Pedro Antonio Moya García

### FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Graduated in computer engineering at the University of Alicante and web and mobile application developer with more than three years of experience, constantly looking for new challenges.

Alicante native passionate about travel and enjoying nature in the company of friends, discovering new routes and destinations where he can get lost in his free time.

### EXPERIENCE

**FULL-STACK DEVELOPER** 

#### **FULL-STACK DEVELOPER** Oct 2022 - Present Petrofac | Leiden, Netherlands

- · Creation of an ERP based on .NET Blazor dedicated to user management, in which I perform Front-End and Back-End tasks.
- · Application developed from scratch based on the latest version of .NET Blazor and using a non-relational database in Azure CosmoDB.

### FormelD | Cologne, Germany · Development and maintenance of an ERP developed in

Sep 2021 - Oct 2022

- Angular 13 and .NetCore 6 and the database in SQL Server.
- · Development of hybrid applications in Xamarin, both for IOS and Android.

#### **FULL-STACK DEVELOPER** Sep 2020 - Sep 2021 Gestión Tributaria Territorial | Alicante, Spain

- · Company collaborating with the Public Administration dedicated to the development of web applications for citizen management.
- Company in which I have acquired knowledge of both Front End (xml, html) and Back End (SQL, Oracle, C#, WCF, JavaScript) and version control through Git.

### Sep 2018 - Feb 2019 **FUL-STACK DEVELOPER** Actio | Alicante, España

- · Actio is a consulting firm specialising in the development and implementation of business management software solutions.
- Company in which I was trained in Back End languages (TypeScript, C#, MySQL, Rest (API), Front End (HTML, CSS) as well as several projects in Angular.

### EDUCATION

#### **DEGREE IN COMPUTER** Sep 2014 - 2020 **ENGINEERING** University of Alicante | San Vicente, Alicante

Bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering (Software

specialisation) **COMPUTER ENGINEERING** Jan 2018 - Jun 2018

Gdansk University of Technology | Polonia, Gdansk

Erasmus studies in Computer Engineering where I acquired a great ability to communicate in English and knowledge about

software encryption, Java applications and other technologies.

### **PROJECTS**

## N1+

- · Winner of the contest of the University of Alicante against gender violence, with recognition from the Diputación de Alicante.
- mobile platforms (Android and IOS) and its corresponding web application in .NET. Currently the application belongs to the University of

• Made in Ionic, Angular and MySQL and developed for both

Alicante, which continues to develop it under the name of Seguras, as an innovation project against gender violence.

### **Foodapet**

- Multiplatform e-commerce for the sale of pet products.
- Made in Ionic for the mobile part (IOS and Android) and
- Use of NoSQL database (Firebase).

.NET for the web part.

CERTIFICATES & COURSES

testing with JUnit and Selenium.

 Completion of a Java and SQL course in which I received knowledge about advanced parts of this language such as

JPA, Spring, Spring Batch, Java EE, Mockito and code